cebuanas.com 2019-06-09

# Cebuanas.com Privacy Policy Statement

This Privacy Policy Statement of [www.Cebuanas.com](https://www.cebuanas.com/) discloses privacy practices of the Cebuanas.com web site in the use of information gathered when a site visitor sign up and becomes a member. Cebuanas.com is an online dating site dedicated to YOU Filipina ladies make your dream come true by helping you find the foreign husband you dream of. Cebuanas are beautiful Filipina women living in the Island of Cebu, Philippines. Cebuanas online dating site is here to assist you in your search of love without fear about your privacy.

Membership to [www.cebuanas.com](https://www.cebuanas.com/) site requires you to fill up online sign up form that ask you to provide information reasonably necessary for you to effectively participate in our Online Dating. 

### I. Children's Privacy

Children are not eligible to join or use our services. This website is not intended for use by children or individuals under the **age of 18** and we do not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information from such people. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected Personal Information from an individual under the **age of 18** , we will immediately delete such information from our database.

### II. What information our site gathers/tracks about you?

Cebuanas.com gathers two (2) types of information:   
1\. Information users voluntarily submit to us; and  
2\. Information indirectly submitted to us by users. 

There are two two (2) types of user-submitted information we collect: Public and Private. 

Cebuanas.com define PUBLIC information as personal information that may be displayed on the site, such as age, gender, height, country of residence, but can not be used to define any member's real identity. PRIVATE information is defined as any information that allows others to contact the user other than through the site or allows collection of information about the user other than what is displayed in the member's profile. 

### A. Private Information

This information is gathered from members who sign up for membership in our online dating site. This information includes email address, first name, last name, birth date, contact number, credit card number and billing information (if any), and the user-specified password. 

We also keep track of your IP ADDRESS every time you visit our Website. Part of your private profile is your IP address upon sign up and every time you use our site facilities. 

### B. Public Information

To accomplish our goal of bringing compatible people together and/or make profile searches easier, we feel that it is imperative that we must gather personal information such as your own photos, birth date, gender, height, weight, hair and eye color, ethnicity or nationality, country of residence, zodiac sign, marital status, education and occupation. This information is meant to be displayed in searches. 

### III. What are the options available to site members who wish to correct, change or discontinue their site membership?

1\. Our Website gives registered members options to correct or change or update information displayed in the members PROFILE. To correct, modify or change Profile Display and Personal Ad login to the site using your unique USER ID and PASSWORD and click Update Profile. 

2\. Our Website is a membership at will and there is never any obligation to remain a registered member. Should you wish to remove any photos or totally deactivate your membership, please send your request via the CONTACT US link/page to reach our friendly LiveHelp to assist and walk you through and help you with your concerns and questions. 

3\. When you choose to discontinue or terminate your membership for any reason, Cebuanas.com reserves the right to keep all photos in the database for whatever administrative and or legal purpose it may serve us best. 

### IV. How do we secure your information in the use of credit cards?

Cebuanas.com website features a secured server with encryption capabilities. We do not keep copies of your credit card data and/or billing information when you use your credit card to pay us. What we do retain for our records are: your transaction ID, cardholder name, and email address so that we are able to communicate with you. No other data, not even your card number, is saved anywhere in our database.

We use the latest security technology to help protect you, our members, and your credit card. We use Godaddy SSL Certificates to protect customer data as it is being transmitted to and from the web server. Transactions on the site are protected with up to 256-bit Secure Sockets Layer encryption. We are in compliance with the Payment Card Industry (PCI) standards to effectively protect and secure our customers credit card information and online transactions. We also employ Trust Guard PCI Security Scanning defense to protect Cebuanas.com website from external attacks which might jeopardize transaction safety.

### Our Security Seals:

Should you have further questions about the security at our website, you can send an email via CONTACT US link.   

### V. Use of Cebuanas.com Dating Site

Your USE of Cebuanas.com website indicates your conformity of our [Terms and Conditions of Use](https://www.cebuanas.com/faq/terms.php) (TCU). Your exclusive use of our website and your dealings with other members of our site will be kept strictly confidential. Moreover, Cebuanas.com makes web chat rooms, messaging, blog and other online facility available to site members. Please be aware, however, that any, and all information you disclosed in these areas becomes public information and Cebuanas.com do not monitor the exchanges of information nor make logs of such information. THEREFORE, we enjoin all members who enjoy our online facilities such as chat rooms and online messaging to exercise due diligence and caution when sharing personal information. 

### VI. Web Chat Rooms and Messaging Policy

Information that you provide on web chat rooms and messaging may not be viewable by the public, but individuals receiving such messages may use or disclose to other individuals or entities; and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications, without our control and without your knowledge. We cannot be responsible for any Personal Information you choose to post on chat and messaging, or send in private messages, and we recommend careful consideration before you post such information.

### VII. Links to Other Site

In any event in the use of www.Cebuanas.com website where there are sites links that may of interest to you, Cebuanas.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or terms of use of these sites. We encourage you to please review the site's privacy policy and terms of use of the site you choose to browse outside Cebuanas.com website. 

### VIII. Use of Google Analytics

Cebuanas.com website uses Google Analytics to generate detailed statistics about our website's traffic and traffic sources to help us understand website performance and usage. Our use of Google Analytics is "anonymized" to avoid Google from tracking the visit and personal data collected via the user's IP address.

You can opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or use the opt-out service provided by Google.

### IX. Changes in our Privacy Policy

If our privacy policy changes in a way that will materially affect our users, we will notify you by posting a notice of the changes on the site. 

### X. LEGAL DISCLAIMER

DUE TO THE VERY NATURE OF INTERNET USE AND EXCHANGES OF INFORMATION EITHER IN THE CHAT ROOMS, MESSAGING OR EMAIL MESSAGES, THERE ARE INHERENT ISSUES RELATING TO THE SECURITY AND PRIVACY OF INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE. WHEN YOU OPT TO USE OUR SITE, YOU RELEASE US FROM ANY AND ALL LIABILITIES RELATING TO YOUR USE OF OUR CEBUANAS.COM WEBSITE. Please review our [Terms and Conditions of Use.](https://www.cebuanas.com/faq/terms.php)
